我们可能会从人类如何解决这个问题中获得灵感;我们非常好
We might take some inspiration for how human beings solve this problem; we're very good
在三维世界中理解和运作。事实上人类使用
at understanding and operating in the three dimensional world. In fact human beings use
大量不同的技巧，技巧，有时称为视觉线索，要理解
a large number of different techniques, tricks, sometimes called visual cues, to understand
三维结构。
three-dimensional structure.
在这篇特别的论文中已经确定了其中的九篇。不同的线索运作
Nine of them have been identified in this particular paper. Different cues operate in
不同的距离制度。认为有一些在我们的武器中是有效的
different distance regimes. Thought there are some that are effective within our arms
到达，一些有效达数十米，有些是有效的，直到地平线，
reach, some are effective up to tens of meters and some are effective right out to the horizon,
距离很多公里。
a distance of many kilometres.
让我们来看看其中的一些视觉线索。最简单的是遮挡，和
Let's have a look at some of these visual cues. The simplest of all is occlusion, and
此信息来自另一个对象前面的对象。我们可以告诉这里
this information comes from what object is in front of another object. We can tell here
那只猫在砖门柱前面，因为猫阻挡了一些遮挡了一些
that the cat is in front of the brick gatepost because the cat blocks out of obscures some
那个门柱和鲜花都在猫的前面，因为它们阻挡了一些猫。
of that gatepost and the flowers are in front of the cat because they block out some of the cat.
另一个重要提示是视野中的高度。看着这个我们可以看到一棵树和
Another important cue is height in the visual field. Looking at this we can see a tree and
我们知道树很重要。但是在这个特定的图像中，树看起来并不像
we know a tree's a pretty big thing. But in this particular image the tree does not look
那么大，所以我们认为这棵树必须走很远的路。
that big, so therefore we figure that the tree must be a long way away.
我们也有相对的大小。我们这里有很多树。在我们的大脑中可能存在
We also have relative size. Here we have a number of trees. In our brain there's probably
某种逻辑说这些是树木，树木都是一样的
some sort of logic that says that these are trees, trees are all going to be the same
因此，这棵看起来比另一棵树大的树必须离我们最近。
size, so therefore, this tree which looks bigger than the other tree must be closest to us.
在这些引人注目的图片中，我们的大脑暂时混淆了。这需要一点时间
In these eye catching pictures, our brain is momentarily confused. It takes a moment
让我们弄清楚接近相机的小东西是什么
for us to figure out what are the small things that are close to the camera and what are
远离相机的大件物品。
the large things that are far away from the camera.
这是沙漠中的一块大石头的照片，只是看着它，这是相当难的
Here's a picture of a large stone in the desert and just looking at it, it's rather hard for
我们要以任何绝对的方式来衡量，这块石头有多大，我们可以打破这种错觉
us to gauge in any sort of absolute way, how big this stone is and we can break the illusion
通过介绍我们知道的尺寸;一双手指，我们可以挑选这块石头
by introducing something whose size we know; a pair of fingers and we can pick this stone
我们可以把它与它更着名的大哥哥，世界上最大的石头，
up and we can compare it to its more famous big brother, the largest stone in the world,
在澳大利亚的中心叫乌鲁鲁。
called Uluru in the centre of Australia.
在这里，我们看到一种非常非常强大的错觉。但是看起来没什么关于这个房间的。
Here we see a very, very powerful illusion. But nothing about this room is, as it seems.
一开始，地板不平坦。现在跟着我，看看它的样子
For a start the floor is not flat. Now follow me in and see what it looks like from the
内。时钟实际上不是圆的;如果我们看看那些我们看到的方形地砖
inside. The clock is not actually round; if we look at those square floor tiles we see
他们实际上并不是正方形的。房间的角落不是直角。
that they are not actually square. And the corners of the room are not right angles.
房间的整体几何形状已经设计出来，因此从这个特定的角度来看
The whole geometry of the room has been contrived, so that from this one particular viewpoint
它看起来像一个普通的房间。
it looks like an ordinary room.
我们用来估算距离的另一种技术称为“纹理密度”，这是一个很好的例子
Another technique we use to estimate distance is called "Texture Density" and a good example
在这条砾石路上可以看到它。近距离我们可以看到各个部分
of it is seen here in this gravel path. Up close we can see the individual pieces of
砾石和越来越远的距离，砾石碎片在图像中变得越来越小。
gravel and at increasing distance the pieces of gravel get smaller and smaller in the image.
近距离纹理非常粗糙，随着我们走得更远，纹理变得更加精细
Up close the texture is quite coarse and as we go further away the texture becomes finer
更精细，所以在我们的眼睛和大脑中，我们正在观察纹理和制作的大小
and finer, so in our eyes and our brain, we're looking at the size of a texture and making
关于距离如何相关的一些假设。
some assumptions about how that relates to distance.
我们在非常大的距离上使用的技术称为空中透视。这个
A technique that we use over very, very large distances is called aerial perspective. This
利用距离为千米级的物体，
exploits the fact that objects that are at large distances of the order of kilometres,
变得不那么明显;更朦胧。
become less distinct; more hazy.
一个非常重要的暗示是双眼差异，我们将更多地谈论它
A really important cue is binocular disparity and we're going to talk much more about it
在这个讲座中。这是从两个场景的两个视图得到的信息
in this lecture. This is the information that’s derived from two views of the scene from two
不同的观点;我们的左眼和右眼，这是一种非常的技术，
different viewpoints; our left eye and our right eye and it's a technique that is very,
广泛用于动物。
very widely used in animals.
我们的眼睛包含一个镜片，我们大脑中有一个相当自主的部分负责保持
Our eye contains a lens and  there’s  a fairly autonomous part of our brain is responsible for keeping
那个镜头聚焦了，所以如果我们正在寻找近距离的东西，那么这部分就是我们的
that lens focused, so if we're looking at something that's up close, this part of our
大脑将调整镜头的形状，以便我们可以专注于该物体。
brain is going to adjust the shape of the lens so that we can focus on that object.
如果物体离得更远，那么镜头的形状将会改变以专注于那个。
If the object is further away, then the shape of the lens is going to be changed to focus on that.
我们可以从这个肌肉中获取信息，并将其作为距离的代表
We can take information from this muscle and use that as a proxy for the distance of the
宾语。我们的视觉系统还有另一个相当自治的部分，它负责
object. There is another fairly autonomous part of our visual system, which is responsible
用于控制我们的眼睛指向的方向。当物体靠近我们的脸时，
for controlling direction in which our eyes point. When an object is close to our face,
我们的眼睛聚集在那个特定的物体上。如果我们获取有关方向的信息
our eyes converge on that particular object. If we take information about the direction
那些是眼睛指向的，我们可以对物体进行三角测量，这是一种推断其距离的方法。
that are eyes are pointing, we can triangulate to the object and that is a way of inferring its distance.
我们使用的最终技术称为“运动视角”，就像我在移动一样
The final technique that we use is called "Motion Perspective" and that is as I'm moving
通过这个世界，靠近我的物体似乎移动得很快，
through the world, objects that are close to me, appear to be moving quite quickly,
而远处的物体似乎移动得慢得多。
whereas objects that are far away, appear to move much more slowly.